Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
- Murtaugh, Patricia, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Mussenden, Lydia Williams GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Muth, Ann Bode, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Myerly, Lois (Greir), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Myers, Anne, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Myers, Ethel (Potteriger-Schoonmaker), 1935 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Myers, Frances Goldberg, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Myers, Joan, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Mynott, Nancy Shiavone Mar, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Nafarian, Pergrouhi GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Nagler, Dorotha GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Nardi, Rose Anna, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Narsutis, Dr. Jessie Bateman Barnes, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Naylor, Helen, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Naylor, Rose Anna, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Needell, Barabara, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Neff, Mildred E., 1924 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Neilson, Doris Wunsch, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Nelson, Anne (Plass), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Nelson, Clara, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Nelson, Eloise Crosby, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Nelson, Helen Y, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Nelson, Lois. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Nelson, Marjorie Kane, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Nettles, Grace Noble, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Neugart, Zelma MS, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Nevin, Therese E. (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Newell, Margaret, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Newman, Dr. Katherine J. (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Newman, Julia Ann (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Newman, Julie (Robb), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Newman, Norma GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Newton, Rosetta, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Nichols, Esther Smith, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Nicholson, Margaret (Saxe), 1930 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Nickerson, Cynthia, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Nickse, Ruth S., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Niederpruem, Marion A. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Nightingale, Erma, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Nilam, Nita GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Nisbet, Betsy Jane, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Nolan, Francena L. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Nolin, Albert, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Norton, Kathryn (Barrett), 1928 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Noyes, Lois Patterson, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Oakley, Geraldine Lockwood, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- O'Brien, Amelia M., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- O'Connell, Clara (Savage), 1934 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- O'Connor, Arlene, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- O'Connor, Arlene O'Hara, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- O'Connor, Carolyn Creamer, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- O'Connor, SalIy, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- O'Connor, Ursula GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- O'Donnell, Dorothy C., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Oesleby, Elizabeth (Denman), 1928 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Ogden, Mille, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Ogle, Betty (Luther), 1948 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Ogle, Wynn, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Olesen, Elizabeth W., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Olsen, Helen, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Olsen, Helen J., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Oniskey, Doris (Caretti), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Opdyke, Evel, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Orrego, Dorothy Benjamin, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Ortmann, Nancy Hunt, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Osborn, Elaine Seeger, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Osborn, Lois, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Osgood, Barbara Travis, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Ostrum, Mary Beth, 1951 (Box 11)
- Oudheusden, Jeanne Griffiths, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Overly, Darlene GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Owens, Charlotte (Beach), 1926 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Owens, Emily GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Paddock, Shirley Lewis, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Padgham, Rose, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Page, Eleanor Pearse, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Paine, Gwendolyn Chapmann, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Palmer, Genevieve Cothran, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Palmer, Hazel (Pearce), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Palmer, Jacqueline Pudish, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Palmer, James B, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Palmer, Julie, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Palmer, Margaret, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Palmer, Mildred (Brucker), 1926 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Palmer, Rhea (Brown), 1935 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Palmes, Rebecca, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Panzarella, Virigina (Pease), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Paolini, Elsie (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Pape, Ann, 1945 (Box 11)
- Pape, Dolores H., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Papenfus, Leslie J., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Pardee, Jean, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Parker, Doris L GR (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Parker, Shirley (Kunz), 1956 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Parsons, Janet Harkness, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Parsons, Marion, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Parsons, Marion Beatty, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Passman, Sandra, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Patchen, Barbara Kane, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Patterson, Irene (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Patterson, Roberta (Losey) (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Paulison, Kathryn D., 1926 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Paxton, Laura Lea, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Payne, Constance Price, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Pearlman, Esther, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Pearson, Elizabeth Woodson, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Pease, Damaris PhD, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Peeler, Janet Eagle, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Peet, Elizabeth, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Peet, Hope (Stevenson), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Peet, Hope Stevenson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Pegues, Nancy Elwin, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Pelletier, Leona Bledsoe GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Pendergast, Agnes L., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Pendleton, Marilyn Davies, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Penn, Jean (Schlafer), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Perduyn, Charlotte, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Perl, Phyllis, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Perry, Arleen Heidgerd, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Perry, Jean Morrison, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Personius, Catherine, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Personius, Deborah, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Pertulo, Vieno, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Peterson, Eleanor (Schaeffer), 1932 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Peterson, Helen (Hilbert), 1941 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- Petrey, Genevieve Frederick, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Petrillose, Sharon (Follett), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Pettem, Jane, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Petterson, Marian Kibbe, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Pettibone, Erna (Kley), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Pettit, Marie, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Pew, Elizabeth Westin, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Pfund, Marion (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Phaneuf, Joan (Hoyland), 1956 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Phelps, Dorothy, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Phillips, Helen F., 1921 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Phillips, Mary (Dodds), 1939 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Philo, Jean, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Pierce, Elizabeth Ann, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Pierce, Janet, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Pieters, Norma (Kenfield), 1933 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Pilcher, Priscilla, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 90)
- Pilcher, Priscilla B., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Pilger, Mary Anne Farrell, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Pinchbeck, Ethelyn, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 91)
- Pineiro, Yolanda, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Pineo, Marion Mac Donald, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Plass, Helen (Palmer), 1948 (Box 7, Folder 92)
- Plass, Helen Palmer, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Platto, Barbara Ira, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Plumis, Ariadne, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Plunkett, Joan, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Podgainy, Marilyn (Spiner) BS, MS, 1957, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 93)
- Poley, Ethel Baer, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Polkinghorne, Edith Freeman GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Polson, Robert A. (Box 7, Folder 94)
- Pomerance, Harriet, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Pond, Nellie W., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 95)
- Poole, Agnes (Ronaldson), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 96)
- Poor, Gladys, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 97)
- Porter, Blaine GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Potter, Bernard, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 98)
- Potter, Jean, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 99)
- Potter, Margaret Smith, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Powell, Elizabeth, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 100)
- Powers, Alice GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Powers, Constance (Sheedy), 1935 (Box 7, Folder 101)
- Powers, Mrs. Virginia (Robords), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 102)
- Powers, Patricia A. Connery, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Pratt, Delia Alden, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Pratt, Mrs. Schuyler (Box 7, Folder 103)
- Pratt, Terrace (Morgan), 1931 (Box 7, Folder 104)
- Prellevitz, Margery Stevenson, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Preston, Ester, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Prey, Dorothy Taylor, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Prince, Rayma Kale (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Prince, Rayma Price, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Pringle, Jane, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 107)
- Pritchard, John, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 108)
- Proud, Dorothy M. (Box 7, Folder 109)
- Prozeller, Mary, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Prytherch, Eunice H., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Purchase, Mary MS, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 111)
- Purdy, Harriet Friemel, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Pyne, Marion MS, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Quartararo, Sara, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 112)
- Quillman, Charles Jr. (Box 7, Folder 113)
- Quinn, Ethel GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Raiber, Laurine, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Raimon-Wilson, Ruth (Amsden), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 114)
- Ranck, Nancy M., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Rankin, Helen GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Rasmussen, Edith Josephine (Svoboda), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 115)
- Rathbun, Lucy Ann, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Rausch, Martha L., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Ray, Elizabeth, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 116)
- Raynor, Jean, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Reading, Nancy, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Ready, Evelyn Walker, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rebollo, Patricia D, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 117)
- Reed, Hazel, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 118)
- Reed, Hazel (Box 7, Folder 119)
- Reederisch, Constance, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Reeves, Mary Louise, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 120)
- Regelman, Mary Ellen Gillet, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Reiger, Carolyn J., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Reiher, Judith (Gold), 1946 (Box 7, Folder 121)
- Reiner, Lillian (Myers), 1929 (Box 7, Folder 123)
- Reinke, Elizabeth (Hannum), 1944 (Box 7, Folder 122)
- Requardt, Gustav J. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Rettinger, Phyllis, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Reynolds, Marcia P., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Rhodes, Kathleen (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Ribe, Melva Wiedemann, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Rice, Andrew (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Rice, Elizabeth J., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rice, Joan B. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Rich, Helen, 1938 (Box 11)
- Rich, Ruth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Richards, Louise, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Richardson, Eleanor, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Riddell, Virginia, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Ridder, Clara A. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Ridley, Carol A. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Riggs, Faith Winne, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Riley, Martha, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Ringholm, Barbara (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Ripley, Helen, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Risley, Marjorie Utz, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ritchey, Hazel, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Rivers, Joseph D., 1921 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Rives, Marilynn Carol, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Rivoire, Alice, 1941 (Box 11)
- Robbins, Ruth Vanderwark, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Roberson, Nena GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Roberts, Betty, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Roberts, Betty Jane Harris, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Roberts, Carolyn, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Roberts, Irene GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Roberts, Mary Ann, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Roberts, Mrs. Mary, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Robeson, Ms. Ellen B. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Robinson, Donna, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Robinson, Elsie, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Robinson, Margaret Blackburn, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Robinson, Thelma D, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Robinson, Thelma Drake, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Robinson, Veronica A. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Rockwell, Cynthia Ide, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Rockwood, Catherine A. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Rodger, Jean, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Roese, Minna (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Roger Fundraising-Sloan (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Roll, Charlotte, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Rolleston, Barbara Sherman (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Romero, Elvin, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Ronaldson, Agnes S., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Ronto, Dorothy, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Roof, Celeste, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Rose, Eleanor J., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Rose, Muriel, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Rosenberg, Peggy, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Rosenblatt, Helene, 1994 (Box 11)
- Rosenthal, Nancy, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Rosner, Gertrude, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Rosse, Roxanne, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Rostoff, Mildred, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Roth, Mrs. Beverly D., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Rothrock, Mary Steadman, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Rothschild, Carolyn (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Rounds, Mary Ann, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Rowe, Ellen, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Rowe, Ellen Baltzell, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rowe, Phyllis Reuning, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Royer, Elizabeth Hershey, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Rubin, Hillary Brown, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Rubin, Marqery B., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ruch, Patricia Hoke, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Ruckle, Margueritte, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Ruffing, Ann Framton, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Rummler, Katherine, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Rumpf, Mary E., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Rumsey, Nancy Hillyer, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Russell, Elaine, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Ryan, Anne E., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Ryan, Mary (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Rystedt, Greta, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Sabin, Helene Freund, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Sacha, Mary Marion, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Sai, Florence A. GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Salinger, Harriett, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Salisbury, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 11)
- Salisbury, Marion R. (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Salissbury, Dorothy Cross, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Saltford, Beatrice, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Salzberg ,Martha Jean, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Sampson, Dorothy Peck (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Samson, Ethel W. (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Samson, Paula, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Sand, Mavis G, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Sanders, Dorothy, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sandur, Dorothy, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Sandwick, Gladys, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Sanford, Jeanne GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Sanjur, Diva PhD, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Sanne, Mary Murrell, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Sappenfield, Rita Cummins, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Sargent. Shirley Richards, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Satina, Wilhelmina Mazar, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Saunders, Jocelyn Gurley, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Saunders, Marjorie, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Savery, Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Sawyer, June C., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Sawyer, Ruth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sawyer, Sally (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Saxe, Ellen M., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sayer, Shirley Howard, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Schaeffer, S.J., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Schaer, Margaret M., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Schaufler, Beverly Pratt, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Scheidelman, Betty, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Schermerhorn, Louise, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Schiller, Edna Wiggins GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Schlater, Jean Davis GR (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Schlerf, Barbara Haglund, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Schlesinger, Benjamin GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Schmidt, Joan D., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Schneider, Carolee, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Schneider, Marilyn, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Schneider, Micki Lasky, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Schneiderman, Nanette Zorn, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Schoen, Margaret, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Schofield, Sally Bickford, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Schoonmaker, Elizabeth Schra, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Schubert, Florence Marjorie (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Schuleen, Ruth, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Schultz, Ruth Anne, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Schunk, Norma MS, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Schus, Stephanie, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Schuster, Margaret, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Schwarting, Barbara Baker, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Schweiger, Leslie, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Schworer, Mary, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Scott, Helen, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Scott, Helen Kerruich, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Scott, Marion, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Scott, Marjory (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Scott, Naomi George, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Scoville, Patricia (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Scudder, Frances A., 1924 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Scutt, Sharma G., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Seaburg, Ellen (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Seaburg, Nellie C., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Searls, Isobel MS, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Seastrand, Joan, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Seebald, Gladys McKeever, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Seel, Marion, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Seeley, Mary Louise, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Seerkus, Barbara J., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Seifert, Bertha Schaffel, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Seitz, Bonnie, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Selby, Betty Hartman, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Seligamn, Dorothy Newman, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Selke, Elizabeth GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Sels, Addie May, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Semanek, Jane, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Senuk, Olga, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sequerth, Ann Gleason, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Sequin, Jean, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Serafine, Catherine, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Serbell, Sally, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Serman, Mary M., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Sester, Carole (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Settembrini, Mary Elizabeth G, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Sexaner, Christine, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sha, Carlton C. (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Shaben, Lillian (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Shackelton, Alberta, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Shah, Iffat GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Shannon, Karen, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Shao, Ho-King GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Shapero, Rosalyn, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Shapiro, Gloria, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sharpe, Sandra Taylor, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Shaul, Eunice Goodman, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Shaver, Frances, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Shaw, Agnes R. GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Shaw, Ann, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Sheerer, Elizabeth GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Sheldon, Elizabeth Rich, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Shepherd, Lynne Bechtold, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Shepperd, Patricia, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Sherlock, Barbara, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Sherman, Caroline (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Sherman, Mary M., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Shevrin, Howard GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Shields, Judith B. GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Shineman, Edward W. and Doris, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Shively, Audrey GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Short, Patricia, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Short, Patricia Mooney, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Shure, Myrna B. PhD, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Sibson, Sandra MS, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Sickles, Jean H, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Siddiqi,Fahmida Jeelani GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Sidney, Phyllis, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Siegel, Judith Engle, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Sielbach, Faye, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sigety, Katharine Snell, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Silvers, Edith, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Simenstad, Ellen, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Sims, Dorothy, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Sine, Mrs. Hilda (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Singson, Maria Pacita MS, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Sinha, Vimla S. PhD, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Sirohi, Narenetra S. GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Sitton, Dorothy Price (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Siudzinski, Marion Hall, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Skellenger, Marie GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Skelton, Elnora Thomas, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Skinner, Margaret Shipman, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Skolnick, Carole, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Slocum, Pearl, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Slocum, Ruth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Slutz, Elizabeth, 1935 (Box 11)
- Smiles, Bonni, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Smiley, Barbara P. (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Smiley, Katherine, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Smillie, David GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Smillie, David GR (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Smith Marian V, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 86)
- Smith Mary, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 87)
- Smith, Elizabeth Klees, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Smith, Elizabeth Logan, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Smith, Harriett S., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Smith, Helen, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Smith, Iva Miller (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Smith, Judth Babis, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Smith, Katharine Messler, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Smith, Katherine Duddy (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Smith, Lowell E., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Smith, Margaret Belknap, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Smith, Marian Michaelis, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Smith, Mildred, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Smith, Miriam, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Smith, Susan Finn, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Smith, Virginia, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Smithells, Jancis GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Smitth, Virginia Brown, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Smoots, Margaret L., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Smulson, Mark (Box 8, Folder 88)
- Smythe, Katherine D., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Snelbecker, Glenn E. PhD, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- Snell, Julia, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Snellman, Adaline GR (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Snipper, Muriel, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Snow, Phyllis R. (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Snyder, Faith, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Snyder, Janet Bliss, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Snyder, Jean K. MS, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Snyder, Marion Silsby, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Solberg, Charlotte L., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Somers, Wynn (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Spaid, Jean Paddock, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Spaid, John F. (Box 8, Folder 94)
- Spar, Mary Russell, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sparling, Charlotte (Box 8, Folder 95)
- Spector, Rita Fingold, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Spencer, Beverly Parsons, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Spencer, Mrs. John House, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Speno, Audre Bernichon, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Sperber, Evelyn Wagner, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Spiegel, Margot, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sprague, Mrs. Helena, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- Spratt, Frances M., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- Sproit, Nancy, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Sprole, Mrs. Robert (Box 8, Folder 98)
- St. Laurent, Marian, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 107)
- Stafford, Col Helen R. (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Stantial, Helen (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Stark, Billie, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 101)
- Starr, Janet Elwin, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Stathis, Aphrodite Carvelas, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Stawson, Esther, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 115)
- Steel, Emmajean, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Steele, Virginia M., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Stefani, Rosa GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Steffen, Elizabeth Ann, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Steffen, Marilyn, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Stegman, Nancy, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 102)
- Steidl, Rose MS, PhD, 1949, 1957 (Box 11)
- Steinberg, Arthur L. (Box 8, Folder 103)
- Steininger, Grace FR (Box 8, Folder 104)
- Steinman, Beatrice, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Stephens, Suzanne, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Stephenson, Betty Halpin, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Stern, Arline Bircly, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Steven, Janet, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Stevens, Gilberta A., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Stevens, Helen Baker, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Stevens, Nancy, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Steves, Gail, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Stewart, Alice Martha (Box 8, Folder 105)
- Stewart, Barbara, 1944 (Box 11)
- Stewart, Dorothy M. MS, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Stewart, Edith Van Nostrand, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Stewart, Mary, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Stiles, Lucille W., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 106)
- Stocks, Esther (Box 8, Folder 108)
- Stockton, Jane, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 109)
- Stoll, Alan, 1968 (Box 11)
- Stockton, Jane Overley Lawre, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Stone, June Nickerson GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Stone, Nancy Sprott, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 110)
- Stone, Suzanne, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Storm, Phyllis, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Storvick, Clara, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 111)
- Storvick, Clara GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Story, Mabel R., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Stout, Evelyn E. (Box 8, Folder 112)
- Stout, Phyllis, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Stout, Phyllis, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 113)
- Stowe, Cornelia, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 114)
- Stowe, Cornelia Moyer, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Strangio, Anna, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Strehmow, Judith Gingell, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)